Guide to the Archives Organization File (AOF) Part 5, Section 2: Boxes 23-44 1870-2017
Archives Organization File (AOF) Part 5, Section 2: Boxes 23-44
- United States. War Manpower Commission. Bureau of Training. Training woman power, 1943; Publication (Box 35, Folder 58)
  - Item 1: Training Womanpower, Publication (Box 35, Folder 58)
    By War Manpower Commission. Booklet. Item is in English.
- United Workers Party of America. What next for the American Workers, 1934; Publication (Box 35, Folder 59)
  - Item 1: What Next for the American Workers?, Publication (Box 35, Folder 59)
    By United Workers' Party of America. Item is in English.
- United Workers of America. World-wide fascism or world revolution?, 1934; Publication (Box 35, Folder 60)
  - Item 1: World-Wide Fascism or World Revolution?, Publication (Box 35, Folder 60)
- University of Iowa. College of Business Administration. Bureau of Labor and Management. Guidelines for employee training, 1963; Publication (Box 35, Folder 61)
  - Item 1: Guidelines for Employee Training, Publication (Box 35, Folder 61)
    By Don R. Sheriff. Item is in English.
- University of Iowa. College of Business Administration. Bureau of Labor and Management. Job enlargement, 1963; Publication (Box 35, Folder 62)
  - Item 1: Job Enlargement: A Case Study, Publication (Box 35, Folder 62)
    By J.F. Biggane and Paul A. Stewart. Item is in English.
- University of Iowa. College of Business Administration. Bureau of Labor and Management. Social and Technological Revolution of the Sixties, 1965; Publication (Box 35, Folder 63)
  - Item 1: The Social and Technological Revolution of the Sixties, Publication (Box 35, Folder 63)
    By University of Iowa - College of Business Administration - Bureau of Labor and Management. Booklet. Item is in English.
- University of Nevada. Dept. of Mechanical and Electrical Engineering. Proceedings of the first annual industrial safety conference, 1914; Publication (Box 35, Folder 64)
  - Item 1: The Proceeding of the First Annual Industrial Safety Conference, Publication (Box 35, Folder 64)
    By University of Nevada - Dept. Of Mechanical and Electrical Engineering. Book. Item is in English.
- University of Pittsburgh. Graduate School of Public and International Affairs. Labor policies and the development of international trade, 1966; Publication (Box 35, Folder 65)
  - Item 1: Labor Policies and the Development of International Trade, Publication (Box 35, Folder 65)
    By David A. Morse. Item is in English.
- University of Wisconsin. University Extension Division. School for Workers, 1959; Publication (Box 35, Folder 66)
  - Item 1: The School for Workers, Publication (Box 35, Folder 66)
    By University of Wisconsin - University Extension Division. Item is in English.
- W.E. Upjohn Institute for Community Research. Guaranteed annual wage and business stabilization, 1955; Publication (Box 35, Folder 67)
  - Item 1: The Guaranteed Annual Wage and Business Stabilization, Publication (Box 35, Folder 67)
    By W.E. Upjohn Institute for Community Research. Item is in English.
- W.E. Upjohn Institute for Community Research Position paper of the paper industry in the economy of Kalamazoo County, Michigan, 1954; Publication (Box 35, Folder 68)
  - Item 1: The Position of the Paper Industry in the Economy of Kalamazoo County Michigan in 1954, Publication (Box 35, Folder 68)
- W.E. Upjohn Institute for Community Research. Pre-requisites for a guaranteed annual wage, 1956; Publication (Box 35, Folder 69)
  - Item 1: Prerequisites for a Guaranteed Annual Wage, Publication (Box 35, Folder 69)
- W.E. Upjohn Institute for Employment Research. Management in the scientific age, 1958; Publication (Box 35, Folder 70)
  - Item 1: Management in the Scientific Age: A Conference of the Washington Chapter Society for Advancement of Management, Publication (Box 35, Folder 70)
- Waterfront Employers Union of San Francisco. Pacific Coast Longshoremen's Strike of 1934, Publication (Box 35, Folder 71)
  - Item 1: The pacific Coast Longshormen;s Strike of 1934, Publication (Box 35, Folder 71)
    By Thomas G. Plant. Item is in English.
- William Roy Smith Memorial Fund. How can a union build its program?, 1940; Publication (Box 35, Folder 72)
  - Item 1: How Can A Union Build It's Program?, Publication (Box 35, Folder 72)
    By William Roy Smith Memorial Fund. Item is in English.
- Workers Alliance of California. Factual statement of Workers Alliance of California, 1939; Publication (Box 35, Folder 73)
  - Item 1: We Were Investigated, Publication (Box 35, Folder 73)
    By Workers Alliance of California. Item is in English.
- Workers Library Publishers. Why every miner should be a Communist / by John Pepper, 1928; Publication (Box 35, Folder 74)
  - Item 1: Why evert Miner should be a Communist, Publication (Box 35, Folder 74)
    By John Pepper. Item is in English.
- Workers Party. Incentive pay: the speed-up new style / by Albert Gates, 1941; Publication (Box 35, Folder 75)
  - Item 1: Incentive Pay, Publication (Box 35, Folder 75)
    By Albert Gates. Item is in English.
- Workers Party - Question of unity: between the Workers Party and the Socialist Workers Party / by Albert Goldman, 1947; Publication (Box 35, Folder 76)
  - Item 1: The Question of Unity, Publication (Box 35, Folder 76)
    By Albert Goldman. Item is in English.
- Workers Party. Election Campaign Committee. How to get jobs for all, 1940; Publication (Box 35, Folder 77)
  - Item 1: How to Get Jobs for All, Publication (Box 35, Folder 77)
    By Workers Party. Item is in English.
- Workers Party of America. Blood and Steel: an exposure of the 12-hour day in the steel industry / by Jay Lovestone, 1920; Publication (Box 35, Folder 78)
  - Item 1: Blood and Steel: An Exposure of the 12-Hour Day in the steel industry, Publication (Box 35, Folder 78)
    By Jay Lovestone. Booklet. Item is in English.
- Workers Party of America. Program and constitution, Workers party of America, 1921; Publication (Box 35, Folder 79)
  - Item 1: Program and Constitution: Workers Party of America, Publication (Box 35, Folder 79)
    By Workers' Party of America. Booklet. Item is in English.
- Working Party of America. Underground radicalism: an open letter to Eugene V. Debs, 1923; Publication (Box 35, Folder 80)
  - Item 1: Underground Racialism, Publication (Box 35, Folder 80)
- Workers Party of America. Unemployment: why it occurs and how to fight it, 1924; Publication (Box 35, Folder 81)
  - Item 1: Unemployment: Why it occurs and How to Fight It, Publication (Box 35, Folder 81)
    By Earl R. Browder. Item is in English.
- Workers Party of U.S. War and the workers / by John West, 1935; Publication (Box 35, Folder 82)
  - Item 1: War and the Workers, Publication (Box 35, Folder 82)
    By John West. Item is in English.
- Workers Party of U.S.A. Role of the trade unions: the economic, 1945; Publication (Box 35, Folder 83)
  - Item 1: The Role of the Trade Unions: Their Economic Role Under Capitalism, Publication (Box 35, Folder 83)
    By Workers' Party of America. Item is in English.
- Workers Party of U.S.A. National Education Dept. Problems of party education, 1946; Publication (Box 35, Folder 84)
  - Item 1: Problems of Party Education: A Guide to Educational Work, Publication (Box 35, Folder 84)
    By Workers' Party of the U.S.A. Item is in English.
- Workers Party of U.S.A. National Education Dept. Workers Party and the transitional program / by Ernest Erber, 1946; Publication (Box 35, Folder 85)
  - Item 1: The Workers Party and the Transitional Program, Publication (Box 35, Folder 85)
    By Ernest Erber. Item is in English.
- Young Workers Communist League. Challenge of youth, 1926; Publication (Box 35, Folder 86)
  - Item 1: The Challenge of Youth, Publication (Box 35, Folder 86)
    By Sam Darcy. Item is in English.
- Allegheny Airline, Publication (Box 36, Folder 1)
  - Item 1: 18th Annual Report 1955, Publication (Box 36, Folder 1)
    By Allegheny Airline. Item is in English.
- American Airlines - Annuals reports, Publication (Box 36, Folder 2)
  - Item 1: Annual Report: Year ended December 31, 1949, Publication (Box 36, Folder 2)
    By American Airlines. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: Annual Report: Year Ended December 31, 1950, Publication (Box 36, Folder 2)
  - Item 3: Annual Report 1951, Publication (Box 36, Folder 2)
  - Item 4: Annual Report 1952, Publication (Box 36, Folder 2)
  - Item 5: Annual Report 1953, Publication (Box 36, Folder 2)
  - Item 6: Annual Report 1956, Publication (Box 36, Folder 2)
  - Item 7: Annual Report 1955, Publication (Box 36, Folder 2)
  - Item 8: Annual Report 1957, Publication (Box 36, Folder 2)
  - Item 9: Annual Report 1954, Publication (Box 36, Folder 2)
- American Airlines - Customer Service Dept., Publication (Box 36, Folder 3)
  - Item 1: Airlines Ticketing System - Questions and Answers, Publication (Box 36, Folder 3)
    By American Airlines - Customer Service Dept. Letter. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: Procedural Revisions, Publication (Box 36, Folder 3)
  - Item 3: Highlights, Publication (Box 36, Folder 3)
    By American Airlines - Customer Service Dept. August 17, 1956. Item is in English.
  - Item 4: Time Limits, Publication (Box 36, Folder 3)
    By American Airlines - Customer Service Dept. Sep 16/56. Item is in English.
  - Item 5: American Airlines Bulletin, Publication (Box 36, Folder 3)
    By American Airlines - Customer Service Dept. August 6, 1956. Item is in English.
  - Item 6: Highlights, Publication (Box 36, Folder 3)
  - Item 7: Highlights, Publication (Box 36, Folder 3)
    By American Airlines - Customer Service Dept. August 17, 1956 Revision No. 6. Item is in English.
  - Item 8: American Airlines Bulletin, Publication (Box 36, Folder 3)
    By American Airlines - Customer Service Dept. August 30, 1956. Item is in English.
  - Item 9: Highlights, Publication (Box 36, Folder 3)
    By American Airlines - Customer Service Dept. Rvision No. 3, September 16, 1956. Item is in English.
  - Item 10: Highlights, Publication (Box 36, Folder 3)
    By American Airlines - Customer Service Dept. Rev. No. 21, August 17, 1956. Item is in English.
- American Airlines - Employee Information, Publication (Box 36, Folder 4)
  - Item 1: Inventroy Questionaire, Publication (Box 36, Folder 4)
    By American Airlines - Employee Information. Form. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: Management Performance Appraisal, Publication (Box 36, Folder 4)
    By American Airlines - Employee Information. Item is in English.
  - Item 3: Summary of Appraisal Interview, Publication (Box 36, Folder 4)
  - Item 4: Quarterly Enter-On and Removal Report, Publication (Box 36, Folder 4)
  - Item 5: Welcome to American, Publication (Box 36, Folder 4)
    By American Airlines - Employee Information. Informational Booklet. Item is in English.
- American Airlines - Management Devel. Dept., Publication (Box 36, Folder 5)
  - Item 1: Management Candidate, Publication (Box 36, Folder 5)
    By American Airlines - Management Level Department. Booklet. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: Management Candidate Guide, Publication (Box 36, Folder 5)
    By American Airlines - Management Level Department. Item is in English.
  - Item 3: Management Candidate Staff Orientation, Publication (Box 36, Folder 5)
    By American Airlines - Management Level Department. June 1958. Item is in English.
  - Item 4: Guide to the Appraisal Process, Publication (Box 36, Folder 5)
  - Item 5: Guide to the Appraisal Process, Publication (Box 36, Folder 5)
    By American Airlines - Management Level Department. Copy 2. Item is in English.
  - Item 6: American Airlines management Development Program - Introduction, Publication (Box 36, Folder 5)
  - Item 7: Phase 11: Group Appraisal, Publication (Box 36, Folder 5)
  - Item 8: Proposals for American Airlines Management Training, Publication (Box 36, Folder 5)
- American Airlines - Organization Charts, Publication (Box 36, Folder 6)
  - Item 1: Buffalo Supervisory Organization, Publication (Box 36, Folder 6)
    By American Airlines - Organization Charts. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: Organization Chart Idewild, Publication (Box 36, Folder 6)
  - Item 3: Letter, Publication (Box 36, Folder 6)
    By C. R. Smith. February 1, 1955. Item is in English.
  - Item 4: Overhaul Division, Publication (Box 36, Folder 6)
  - Item 5: Maintanence & Engineering Department, Publication (Box 36, Folder 6)
  - Item 6: Appendix I - Organization of American Airlines, Publication (Box 36, Folder 6)
  - Item 7: Appendix I - Organization of American Airlines, Publication (Box 36, Folder 6)
    By American Airlines - Organization Charts. Copy 2. Item is in English.
- American Airlines - Miscellaneous, Publication (Box 36, Folder 7)
  - Item 1: Cornell University Business Leadership Course for American Airlines, Publication (Box 36, Folder 7)
    By American Airlines - Miscelleneous. Booklet. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: Cornell University Business Leadership Course, Publication (Box 36, Folder 7)
    By American Airlines - Miscellaneous. Copy 2. Item is in English.
  - Item 3: Cornell University Business Leadership Course, Publication (Box 36, Folder 7)
    By American Airlines - Miscellaneous. Copy 3. Item is in English.
  - Item 4: Cornell University Business Leadership Course, Publication (Box 36, Folder 7)
    By American Airlines - Miscellaneous. Copy 4. Item is in English.
  - Item 5: Planning - Letter, Publication (Box 36, Folder 7)
    By American Airlines - Miscellaneous. November 30, 1955. Item is in English.
  - Item 6: A Look Ahead at the Air Transportation Industry, Publication (Box 36, Folder 7)
    By Dr. T. P. Wright Vice-President for Reasearch Cornell University. Item is in English.
  - Item 7: Panning Publication 1953, Publication (Box 36, Folder 7)
    By American Airlines - Miscellaneous. Item is in English.
  - Item 8: Conference Bulletin No. 169, Publication (Box 36, Folder 7)
    By Frank J. Macklin. July 10, 1956. Item is in English.
  - Item 9: Work Simplification Guide, Publication (Box 36, Folder 7)
    By American Airlines - Miscellaneous. Booklet. Item is in English.
  - Item 10: Work Simplification Guide, Publication (Box 36, Folder 7)
  - Item 11: Work Simplification Guide, Publication (Box 36, Folder 7)
- American Airlines - Sales, Publication (Box 36, Folder 8)
  - Item 1: How to Lick The "Noshow Problem", Publication (Box 36, Folder 8)
    By American Airline Sales. April 2, 1956. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: New Ticketing System Mailings, Publication (Box 36, Folder 8)
    By American Airline Sales. Letter. Item is in English.
  - Item 3: It's so east to Fly American!, Publication (Box 36, Folder 8)
    By American Airline Sales. Pamphlet. Item is in English.
  - Item 4: Letter, Publication (Box 36, Folder 8)
    By C.R. Smith. August 10, 1956. Item is in English.
  - Item 5: Letter to Traveler, Publication (Box 36, Folder 8)
    By American Airline Sales. August 10, 1956. Item is in English.
  - Item 6: Letter to Passenger, Publication (Box 36, Folder 8)
  - Item 7: Letter to Admiral Smith, Publication (Box 36, Folder 8)
    By American Airline Sales. Copy 2. Item is in English.
  - Item 8: Recap of Replies Received in Response to Admirals Mailing Regarding "Confirmed Ticket Pick-Up", Publication (Box 36, Folder 8)
    By American Airline Sales. Item is in English.
  - Item 9: It's so east to Fly American!, Publication (Box 36, Folder 8)
    By American Airline Sales. Yellow Version. Item is in English.
  - Item 10: What the Businessman Thinks of the New Ticketing Procedures, Publication (Box 36, Folder 8)
    By American Airline Sales. booklet. Item is in English.
  - Item 11: Letter to Admiral Smith, Publication (Box 36, Folder 8)
    By American Airline Sales. August 29, 1956. Item is in English.
  - Item 12: Letter to Admiral Smith from The National Life and Accident Insurance Company, Publication (Box 36, Folder 8)
  - Item 13: Letter to Mr. Smith, Publication (Box 36, Folder 8)
    By American Airline Sales. Agust 20, 1956. Item is in English.
  - Item 14: Letter to Mr. Smith from the McGraw-Hill Book Company, Publication (Box 36, Folder 8)
    By American Airline Sales. August 20, 1956. Item is in English.
  - Item 15: Letter to Mr. Smith from the Kellogg Company, Publication (Box 36, Folder 8)
    By American Airline Sales. August 30, 1956. Item is in English.
  - Item 16: Letter to Mr. Smith from Behr-Manning, Publication (Box 36, Folder 8)
    By American Airline Sales. August 16, 1956. Item is in English.
  - Item 17: Letter to Mr. Smith from the North American Lace Co. Inc., Publication (Box 36, Folder 8)
  - Item 18: Letter to Mr. Smith from the Akron, Canton & Youngstown Railroad Company, Publication (Box 36, Folder 8)
  - Item 19: Letter to Mr. Smith from Beaumont Rice Mills, Publication (Box 36, Folder 8)
    By American Airline Sales. August 24, 1956. Item is in English.
  - Item 20: Letter to Mr. Smith from Robert J. Neidlinger Travel Service, Inc., Publication (Box 36, Folder 8)
    By American Airline Sales. August 23, 1956. Item is in English.
  - Item 21: Letter to Mr. Smith from Renfro & Johnson, Publication (Box 36, Folder 8)
  - Item 22: Letter to Mr. Smith from Barrett Divison, Publication (Box 36, Folder 8)
  - Item 23: Letter to Mr. Smith from Siversmiths & Goldsmiths Manufacturing, Publication (Box 36, Folder 8)
    By American Airline Sales. Agust 16, 1956. Item is in English.
  - Item 24: Letter to Mr. Smith from Thomas A. Edison Incorporated, Publication (Box 36, Folder 8)
  - Item 25: Letter to Mr. Smith form R.S.Paviour & Son Inc., Publication (Box 36, Folder 8)
    By American Airline Sales. August 17, 1956. Item is in English.
  - Item 26: Philip Wick Company, Inc., Publication (Box 36, Folder 8)
  - Item 27: Letter to Mr. Smith from Herbert A. Payne, Publication (Box 36, Folder 8)
  - Item 28: Letter to Mr. Smith from the Norton Company, Publication (Box 36, Folder 8)
  - Item 29: Letter to Mr. Smith from Hemingway Bros., Publication (Box 36, Folder 8)
  - Item 30: Letter to Mr. Smith from American Steel & Wire, Publication (Box 36, Folder 8)
  - Item 31: Letter to Mr. Smith from George E. Harding, Publication (Box 36, Folder 8)
  - Item 32: Letter to Mr. Smith from Solvay Process Division, Publication (Box 36, Folder 8)
  - Item 33: Letter to Mr. Smith from the Internuclear Company, Publication (Box 36, Folder 8)
    By American Airline Sales. August 28, 1956. Item is in English.
  - Item 34: Letter to Mr. Smith from Stein-Sulkis Shoe Co., Publication (Box 36, Folder 8)
  - Item 35: Letter to Mr. Smith from the Troy Buick Company, Publication (Box 36, Folder 8)
    By American Airline Sales. August 15, 1956. Item is in English.
  - Item 36: Letter to Mr. Smith from The Hooper- Holmes Bureau, Inc., Publication (Box 36, Folder 8)
  - Item 37: Royal McBee Corporation, Publication (Box 36, Folder 8)
  - Item 38: Letter to Mr. Smith from the Continental Baking Company, Publication (Box 36, Folder 8)
  - Item 39: Letter to Mr. Smith from Stecker Chemicals, Inc., Publication (Box 36, Folder 8)
  - Item 40: Letter to Mr. Smith from the Quigley Publishing Company, Inc., Publication (Box 36, Folder 8)
  - Item 41: Letter to Mr. Smith from DeBardeleben Coal Corporation, Publication (Box 36, Folder 8)
    By American Airline Sales. August 27, 1956. Item is in English.
  - Item 42: Letter to Mr. Smith from LePage's Inc., Publication (Box 36, Folder 8)
  - Item 43: Letter to Mr. Smith from WSYR, Publication (Box 36, Folder 8)
  - Item 44: Letter to Mr. Smith from ACF Industries, Publication (Box 36, Folder 8)
  - Item 45: Letter to Mr. Smith from Paul D. Newton, Publication (Box 36, Folder 8)
    By American Airline Sales. August 22, 1956. Item is in English.
  - Item 46: Letter to Mr. Smith from Rose-Derry Company, Publication (Box 36, Folder 8)
    By American Airline Sales. August 21, 1956. Item is in English.
  - Item 47: Letter to Mr. Smith from Guy C. Myers, Publication (Box 36, Folder 8)
  - Item 48: Letter to Mr. Smith from the Turner Construction Company, Publication (Box 36, Folder 8)
  - Item 49: Letter to Mr. Smith from the Rose-Derry Company, Publication (Box 36, Folder 8)
  - Item 50: Letter to Mr. Smith from the Sheraton Corporation, Publication (Box 36, Folder 8)
  - Item 51: Letter to Mr. Smith from the Detroit Beach Company Inc., Publication (Box 36, Folder 8)
  - Item 52: Letter to MR. Smith from the Colonial Tanning Company, Publication (Box 36, Folder 8)
  - Item 53: Letter to Mr. Smith from United States Envelope Company, Publication (Box 36, Folder 8)
    By American Airline Sales. Augusr 17, 1956. Item is in English.
  - Item 54: Letter to Mr. Smith from Allied Artists Pictures Corporation, Publication (Box 36, Folder 8)
  - Item 55: National Aniline Division, Publication (Box 36, Folder 8)
  - Item 56: Crucible Steel Company of America, Publication (Box 36, Folder 8)
  - Item 57: The No-Show Problem and The Local Service Carriers, Publication (Box 36, Folder 8)
    By C.R. Smith. Item is in English.
- American Cale & Radio Corp. - Union Agreement, Publication (Box 36, Folder 9)
  - Item 1: Agreement between American Cable & Radio Corporation and Communications Workers of America, Publication (Box 36, Folder 9)
    By American Cable & Radio Corp. - Union Agreement. Item is in English.
- American Cable & Radio - AC & R News, Publication (Box 36, Folder 10)
  - Item 1: AC&R News, Publication (Box 36, Folder 10)
    By American Cable & Radio. Vol.1, No.5, August, 1954. Item is in English.
- Anheuser - Busch, Inc., Publication (Box 36, Folder 11)
  - Item 1: Your trip through the home of Budweiser, Publication (Box 36, Folder 11)
    By Anheuser-Busch, Inc. Booklet. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: Your Retirement Income Plan, Publication (Box 36, Folder 11)
    By Anheuser-Busch, Inc. Item is in English.
  - Item 3: Group Insurance Plan, Publication (Box 36, Folder 11)
  - Item 4: Group Insurance Plan, Publication (Box 36, Folder 11)
    By Anheuser-Busch, Inc. Yellow Version - November 1953. Item is in English.
  - Item 5: Preeferred Everywhere Budweiser, Publication (Box 36, Folder 11)
  - Item 6: 100 Years of Quality - Budcaster, Publication (Box 36, Folder 11)
    By Anheuser-Busch, Inc. Vol.1, No.7, September, 1952. Item is in English.
  - Item 7: Budcaster, Publication (Box 36, Folder 11)
    By Anheuser-Busch, Inc. Vol. 3, No.3, Marhc, 1954. Item is in English.
  - Item 8: Labor Agreement, Publication (Box 36, Folder 11)
    By Anheuser-Busch, Inc. Effective March 1, 1953. Item is in English.
  - Item 9: Labor Agreement between the International Union of United Brewery Flour, Cereal, Soft Drink an Distillery Workers of America, CIO, etc. and Anheuser-Busch, Inc., Publication (Box 36, Folder 11)
  - Item 10: Salaried Employees Pension Plan, Publication (Box 36, Folder 11)
- Astrodyne, Inc., Publication (Box 36, Folder 12)
  - Item 1: Compnay Policies, Publication (Box 36, Folder 12)
    By Astrodyne Inc. Item is in English.
- AT & T - Providing Employees Info they want, Publication (Box 36, Folder 13)
  - Item 1: Providing Employees With Information They Want, Publication (Box 36, Folder 13)
    By John W. Cogswell. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: Provising Employees With Information They Want, Publication (Box 36, Folder 13)
    By John W. Cogswell. Copy 2. Item is in English.
- AT & T: The Bell System, Publication (Box 36, Folder 14)
  - Item 1: The Bell System, Publication (Box 36, Folder 14)
    By A.T. & T. Informational Pamphlet. Item is in English.
- Bullard Co. Literature on Employee Benefits, Publication (Box 36, Folder 15)
  - Item 1: Security afer this "Better Job", Publication (Box 36, Folder 15)
    By Bullard Co. Booklet. Item is in English.
  - Item 2: Security after this "Better Job", Publication (Box 36, Folder 15)
    By Bullard Co. Copy 2. Item is in English.